

Luc Nguyen Van

General information

- P June 05th, 1999
- 210 Doi Can St, Ba Dinh, Hanoi, Vietnam
- nguyenluc99.github.io/
- linkedin.com/in/lucnguyen-ict
- luc.nv176812@sis.hust.edu.vn
- nguyenlucitbk@gmail.com

About Me -

I am currently a computer science student. Being interested in mathematics and programming, I love researching computer algorithms. The algorithmic thinking helps me solve problems, not only in computer science and mathematics, but also in real life, more critically and efficiently. Our life would be better and more convenient with better methods and resolutions. Therefore, I enjoy researching algorithms.

Languages -

Vietnamese English



Background -

Graph theory Combinatorics



Computer Science

Technical skills -

Linux C/C++ Java/Python

NodeJS ₽TFX Photography

Education

2017-2023 **Computer Science student**

Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Major CPA 3.46/4.0

Autumn 2020 Exchange student at Uppsala University, Sweden

Awards and honors

2020 One of four Erasmus-Mundus Scholarship 2020 for exchange

student, worth 145 millions VND

2019 Mini-course: Essential Mathematics and Computing for Data

Science, Vietnam Institute for Advanced Study in Mathematics

Research experiences

· Locally-constrained de Bruijn code enumeration in C++: in preparation of publication.

· Dyck Path enumerations: enumeration with customized height of up, down steps, and bounded running height.

Teaching experiences

Fall 2021 **Introduction to Computer** Hanoi University of Science and Technology

Primary teaching assistant of two classes during office hours and lab sections. Prepared lectures, graded assignments and gave weekly feed-

Volume: 60 hours, enrollments: 80 students.

Fall 2021 **C advanced: Programming** Hanoi University of Science and Technology

techniques

Primary teaching assistant of a class during office hours and lab sections. Prepared exercises, graded assignments and gave weekly feedback.

Volume: 30 hours, enrollments: 50 students.

Working experiences

Apr 2022 -C++ Software Engineer OJT Toshiba Software Development Vietnam

Present Mar 2021 -**Machine Learning Engineer** Eastgate Software JSC

Sep 2021

Social activities

2017-2023: Seven-time key member and organizer of "Future career talk show" (An annual warmly talk between high school and university

students) Ø

Member of Volunteer team 10/1985 - Student Union, Hanoi University of Science and Technology. Volunteer at Hanoi Math Open Day. Volunteer at University Entrance Examinations in local high school during 2018-2022.

Interests

Research and contribute to fields of Algorithm, Combinatorics

and Mathematics. Connect with people from other cultures and the world 0

Future goals

>+ Become a computer scientist

Become a globally effective researcher and contributor

Learn several more languages

References

Thuan Do Phan Associate Professor, Faculty of Computer Science.

Hanoi University of Science and Technology.

No.1, Dai Co Viet Street, Hai Ba Trung District, Hanoi City, Vietnam. website: soict.hust.edu.vn/.... thuandp@soict.hust.edu.vn

Van Khu Vu Senior researcher, lecturer in Computer Engineering.

National University of Singapore.

21 Lower Kent Ridge Road, Singapore 119077

website: scholar.google.com/.... isevvk@nus.edu.sg

Huong Tran Thi Thu Lecturer in Mathematics and Computer Science.

Vietnamese-German University.

Ring road 4, Thoi Hoa ward, Ben Cat town, Binh Duong province, Vietnam.

huong.ttt@vgu.edu.vn website: vgu.edu.vn/....

March 29, 2023

Luc Nguyen Van